earnify.com 2016-08-05

# Earnify - Privacy Policy

**EARNIFY PRIVACY POLICY**

**1.** **Introduction**

Thank you for visiting the Earnify website ("Site") and, if applicable, choosing to use any of our services ("Services"). We try to make our Privacy Policy easy to understand so that you are informed as to how we use your information. This Privacy Policy, like our Terms of Service, is an integral part of using our Service; therefore you must completely agree to our Privacy Policy in order to use our Site or Service. You must be over the age of 18 to use the Site and Services. 

**2.** **Information Collected**

Personally Identifiable Information Collected from Users 

In order to use our Service and register for our Site, we may collect your name, email address, telephone number, website information, Skype information, and physical address. Additionally, if you wish to be a publisher via the Service, we may collect your financial and tax information to send payments to you. We may collect any additional information we deem necessary to provide any of our Services to you. 

Non-Identifying Information 

Whenever you use our website, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, interactions with the website, mobile information, log information, device information, query information, location, referring URL, browser, operating system, data usage, data transferred, and Internet Service Provider. We may use additional third party analytic tools to collect non-identifying personal infomation. 

**3.** **Use of Your Information**

We may use your personally identifiable information for the following purposes: 

· To enhance or improve our users' experiences. 

  * To provide our Service to you. 
  * To process transactions and payments. 

· To email you newsletters, marketing, and correspondence from us. 

· To contact you and to respond to inquiries. 

Additionally, we may give your information to law enforcement if we are compelled to by a court order, if there has been a violation of any Australian laws or if a violation of the Terms of Service or Privacy Policy has occurred. 

**4.** **Opt Out, Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information**

You will be able to access any information contained in your account through our Site; however you won't be able to opt out of our information collection practices. In some instances may edit your information by removing or changing the information listed in your account. If you have any questions or wish to review, change, or access any of your information collected by us, please contact us at legal@earnify.com. Except as otherwise stated herein, after you have cancelled your account please be aware that we may keep inaccessible copies of your information for a commercially reasonable period of time. 

**5.** **Cookies**

We use cookies to remember your preferences and advertisements. For these reasons, it is necessary that you enable cookies in your browser, and you hereby acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system. If you wish to block any cookies, you may adjust your browser options to do so. However, blocking cookies may cause errors in our Site. 

**6.** **Third Party Access to Your Information**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with Earnify to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others to allow you to access the Site and Service. 

Throughout the course of our provision of our Services to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you. 

**7.** **Law Enforcement**

You agree that we may disclose your information to authorities if compelled to by a court order. Additionally, you agree that we may disclose your information if we reasonably believe that you have violated Australian laws or the terms of our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy or if we believe that a third party is at risk of bodily harm. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is proper to do so for legal reasons, where your actions violate any law of the Australian or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our Site, Services, or our Terms of Service. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities and to any state or national authorities, as required. 

**8.** **Commercial, Non-Commercial Communications and Do Not Track**

If you decide to provide us with your contact information, you agree that we may send you communications via email. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying Earnify that you no longer wish to receive these communications, we will endeavour to promoptly remove you from our mailing list once we have received that request. We currently do not subscribe to "do not track listings" and do not offer functionality for you to opt out through "do not track" listings. If you wish to opt out of certain communications or information collection, please contact us at legal@earnify.com. 

**9.** **Third Parties**

Earnify or Users may post links to third party websites on our Site or Service, which may include information that we have no control over. When accessing a third party site through our Site or Service, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites. 

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties. Earnify bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. You must review their Terms of Service and Privacy to understand how their information collection practices work. 

**10.** **Security Measures**

We make reasonable attempts to protect your information by using physical and electronic safeguards such as SSL certificates. However, as this is the Internet, we can make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information. For this reason, we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats. 

**11.** **International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. We may transfer personal information to Australia or elsewhere and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

**12.** **Merger and Acquisition**

In the event that Earnify is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. Please be aware that once the information is transferred your privacy rights may change. 

**13.** **Amendments**

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will modify the date listed on this Agreement or we may contact you. You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site and Service. If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site and Service and notify us of your refusal to agree by e-mailing us at legal@earnify.com. 

Last Modified: July 4, 2015
